<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>My Food Porn</title>
  
  <link href="/MyFoodPorn/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/"/>
  <updated>2017-02-25T03:25:04.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Logan Griffis</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Chicken Enchiladas</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/02/24/ChickenEnchiladas/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/02/24/ChickenEnchiladas/</id>
    <published>2017-02-25T03:15:25.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-25T03:25:04.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Chicken Enchiladas with Corn &amp; Black Bean Salsa for Two</strong></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/image_0.jpg" alt="Chicken Enchiladas"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/image_1.jpg" alt="Chicken Enchiladas"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/image_2.jpg" alt="Chicken Enchiladas"></p>
<p><strong>These chicken enchiladas are pretty easy to make;  but, like with most good food, you’ll need time and patience.  It’s the little things in recipes that make a difference, like in this recipe caramelizing the onions until they charred slightly made for the perfect balance of sweet when mixed with the chicken, and boiling the corn in butter and salt to make the final salsa buttery and sweet, and just perfect with a good squeeze of lime. Or if you want a more “roasty” flavor, grill the corn and as it’s piping on the grill squeeze a lime over it and melt a big blob of butter over the cob.  Either way you do the corn, nothing can compare to how good the resulting salsa pairs with the luscious, cheesy, zesty, meaty enchiladas smothered with a cream cheese sauce blended with pureed mild green chillies and baked in a well-seasoned cast iron pan, and don’t forget the copious amounts of lime (seriously, I used about two limes just for the sauce, but it was totally worth it).  Another thing, if you’re on a diet you’ll probably want to avoid this recipe; it’s heavy on the fat, but hey it’s good to indulge every now and then.  The only thing that would make this meal any better would be a homemade margarita, en serio</strong></p>
<p><strong>Ingredients</strong> :</p>
<p><strong>For the Chicken</strong> :</p>
<ul>
<li><p><strong>2-3 chicken breasts</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ a red onion, thinly sliced and caramelized</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>1 tbsp cumin</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ tbsp paprika</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ tbsp oregano</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ tbsp garlic powder</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ tbsp ground coriander (optional)</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Salt and pepper to taste</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Lime juice (for final seasoning in pan)</strong></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>For the Sauce : </strong></p>
<ul>
<li><p><strong>1 block of full fat cream cheese</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>1 small heavy cream</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>1 small can green chilies, pureed in a blender (to better incorporate in the sauce)</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>1-2 limes to taste</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Salt to taste, no pepper (unless you want to)</strong></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>For the Salsa : </strong></p>
<ul>
<li><p><strong>1 cob of roasted, grilled, or butter-boiled corn, kernels shaved off when cooked and cooled</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ can rinsed and drained unseasoned black beans</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ a small red onion, thinly diced</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>1 small, **</strong><em>firm</em><strong>** roma tomato (trust me, a firm tomato makes for a less juicy salsa, and in turn leaves the flavors pure and unmuddied by any excess juices. . . . .  other than the lime juice of course)</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ a jalapeno, thinly diced</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>⅓-¼ cup of roughly chopped cilantro</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>1 squeezed lime</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Salt to taste</strong></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>You could also add a touch of cumin and paprika to the salsa for a slightly roasty taste. </strong></p>
<p><strong>The How-To : </strong></p>
<ol>
<li><p><strong>First boil, roast, or grill your cob of corn.  Whatever method of cooking you use, just make sure you squeeze that lime and melt that butter over it.  You want to cook your corn first so that it has time to cool before you handle it. </strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Next, caramelize your red onion slices over medium-low heat until tender and brown, this should take anywhere from 15-20 minutes, but be patient! It’s worth the time.  Remove the onions, then take your seasoned chicken and sear on high heat in the same pan you plan on making your sauce in.  Once your chicken is nice and crusty on the outside, lower the heat to medium low, squeeze lime over the breasts, and cover to cook on **</strong><em>medium-low </em><strong><em>*heat for about 10 minutes. </em>Tip : Make sure you have a nice hot sear on your meat before you lower the heat, the sear is key to trapping in the chicken’s moisture.  Don’t be afraid of the high heat!  It’s not permanent. </strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong> Remove your chicken to rest and cool on a cutting board.  Add the pureed green chillies to your chicken pan and all it’s chickeny goodness and saute for a bit, then squeeze your lime over the chilis, and liberally salt the mixture.  </strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Finally, for the sauce, cut the cream cheese into chunks (it speeds up the melting process) and add the cheese to the chili-lime mixture. When the cheese is all melted it will be quite thick; that’s where the heavy cream comes in.  Pour the cream in until the sauce meets your desired thickness.  If necessary add a bit of plain milk.  I tend to use the entire container of heavy cream because I like my sauce somewhat runny (for good reason!) because when it bakes it tends to thicken.  Melt the cheese, cream, chili, and lime together and while it incorporates start your salsa. </strong></p>
</li>
</ol>
<p><strong><em> Oh! I forgot, preheat your oven to 350 :D Oops Forgot that little piece of info</em></strong></p>
<ol>
<li><p><strong>For the salsa, shave the corn off its cob and toss it into a mixing bowl, thinly dice your red onion, jalapeno, and tomato, and roughly chop your cilantro, then rinse ½ cup of unseasoned black beans under cold water, and add all this to your hopefully beautiful corn and mix until evenly incorporated. Squeeze a good amount of lime over the forming salsa and season with salt, and a bit of cumin and paprika, if you so desire.  Put aside to top the enchiladas later.</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>By now, your chicken should be well-rested and cooled, shred it as finely as you can and mix it with the caramelized red onions.  Steam about 4-5 tortillas (in the microwave or lightly in the oven; I cheated and used the microwave) and liberally fill each one with the chicken mixture.  Fold each one as they come and settle them in the pan into the sauce.  Once the pan is full try to spoon a bit of the cheese sauce over the enchiladas then pour some salsa verde (you can usually find a good quality store bought salsa verde) directly down the middle of the enchiladas, top with a cheese of your choice and pop them in the oven. </strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Bake them bitches for about 10-15 minutes, or until the sauce is bubbling around the enchiladas and the tortillas are nice and toasty around the edges.  Remove them from the oven to cool for a bit, then profusely top them with your beautiful salsa.  </strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Serve hot, hopefully with a margarita. </strong></p>
</li>
</ol>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chicken Enchiladas with Corn &amp;amp; Black Bean Salsa for Two&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/image_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chicke
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Miso Hot Pot</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/28/MisoHotPot/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/28/MisoHotPot/</id>
    <published>2017-01-29T02:56:22.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-29T04:13:52.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Miso Hot Pot</strong></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/hotPot1.jpg" alt="Miso Hot Pot"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/HotPot2.jpg" alt="image alt text"></p>
<p><strong>Ok, so not to brag or anything, but this hot pot tasted like heaven for tongues. . . . if that’s even possible <em>giggles</em>, tongue heaven, sorry mental image.  Back to the topic at hand; the broth was miso-ey, rich and meaty with bonito and juices from the sweet but kinda spicy marinated beef and ginger/garlic pork meatballs.  And if you’ve never had veggies boiled in such a broth, you’re sorely, I mean **</strong><em>sorely, </em><strong><strong>missing out.  Pair this with freshly steamed rice, and be sure to lay a piece of homemade kimchi over that meat. The flavor almost made me swoon.  And I’m not the swooning type.  My boyfriend laughed at first, tried it, then just shook his head and closed his eyes.  Then did it again, and again, until we were fighting over the last piece of spicy fermented cabbage.  We nitpicked and filled each others bowls with tender meat, succulent vegetables, and rich broth, occasionally adding more meat to the pot, drinking beer and revelling in each others company and the joy of cooking and sharing an excellent meal together.  Do not, for the love of God or Buddha or whoever, eat this alone.  I mean it, </strong></strong><em>no solitary eating</em><strong>** over a dish like hot pot that evolved around the concept of family and communion.  So with that, here we go, let’s make some hot pot!</strong></p>
<p><strong>Ingredients :</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><p>Thinly sliced <strong>eye of round or any type of thinly sliced meat</strong>.  Occasionally I use pork belly or ribeye. Some people use shrimp, clams, or fish to make a seafood hot pot. It’s really up to you and your friends and family’s preferences.  This go round I used some leftover ground pork from some cabbage rolls I made two days back that I had frozen.  Waste not want not and all that jazz.  Oh! And some delicious lean eye of round.</p>
</li>
<li><p>An assortment of <strong>veggies</strong>.  Whatever you like really, I used what I like (naturally), and it was also what I had in my fridge at the time.  Rounds of <strong>napa cabbage</strong>, some <strong>baby bok choy, or pak choi</strong> as the lady at the Asian supermarket kindly informed me, some <strong>broccoli </strong>also went into the mix, as well as some matchstick <strong>carrots</strong> and diced <strong>green onion</strong>. I also added a generous portion of my homemade kimchi as a small side dish, and it’s super healthy for your gut, so go wild!</p>
</li>
<li><p>Some farm-fresh eggs perhaps</p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>Jasmine rice </strong></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>For the Broth :</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><p><strong>About 5-6 cups of water, </strong>enough to fill your hot pot.</p>
</li>
<li><p>About 6 bulbs of <strong>garlic</strong>, and a good inch of <strong>ginger root</strong>, peeled and crushed/finely chopped with the garlic (some of this will go into the meat marinade so save a good <strong>½</strong> tbsp or so).</p>
</li>
<li><p>A fat heaping tablespoon of <strong>light miso</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p>A half sheet of <strong>kombu</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p>A heaping cup of <strong>bonito flakes</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>¼</strong> cup <strong>soy sauce</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p>About <strong>4-5 tablespoons of</strong> <strong>mirin </strong>(sweet rice wine), you can also add a splash of sake if you have it. . . . . and maybe take a shot. . . . or two, or four.  It’s a party right?</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>For the Meat and Marinade :</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><p><strong>½</strong> lb of <strong>ground pork</strong>, if you want to make the meatballs that I did in the pictures.</p>
</li>
<li><p>A pack of <strong>thinly sliced eye of round, or any thinly sliced meat</strong>.</p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>½ </strong>cup of <strong>soy sauce</strong>, both for the pork and other meat that you have.</p>
</li>
<li><p>A splash of <strong>mirin</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p>Finely chopped <strong>green onion and carrots </strong>(for the meatballs)</p>
</li>
<li><p>Some ground <strong>black pepper</strong></p>
</li>
<li><p>About  <strong>⅓**</strong> <strong>a cup </strong>brown sugar**.</p>
</li>
<li><p><strong>One tablespoon</strong> <strong>chili flakes</strong>, or preferably <strong>ground korean chili flakes</strong>.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>The How-to : </strong></p>
<ul>
<li><p>Firstly, soak your half sheet of kombu in the 5-6 cups of water for at least 30-45 minutes.  So you can do this and sit on your ass while it’s soaking, doing whatever.</p>
</li>
<li><p>Or, you could start chopping your veggies.</p>
</li>
<li><p>After your veggies, if you chose this route, you can start your rice.  I recommend rinsing your rice at least twice under cold water before cooking.  This removes any extra starch around the rice kernels and therefore makes the finished product more fluffy and flavorful.  Remember, fluffy rice is always nice.  Oh, just a tip, if you want you can use a rag to cover that annoying hole in your pot while your rice cooks.  This helps trap the moisture and therefore makes your rice fluffier. This is for people who don’t own a rice cooker (ugh I want one so bad).</p>
</li>
<li><p>For the meatballs, mix your pork with about a tablespoon of soy sauce, about <strong>3 heaping tablespoons</strong> of  finely chopped carrot and green onion, about a <strong>tablespoon</strong> of crushed garlic and ginger, a splash of mirin, and some ground pepper and salt.  If you like your meatballs spicy, you can add a touch of korean chili flakes.</p>
</li>
<li><p>After your veggies, rice, and meatball prep you can mix together your meat marinade.  Add the <strong>⅓ </strong>brown sugar, <strong>½ </strong>soy sauce, <strong>6 </strong>garlic bulbs and and an <strong>inch</strong> of ginger (remember to reserve some for the meatballs), <strong>1 tablespoon</strong> of korean chili flakes, that splash of mirin, and some sake if you have it, as well as some roughly chopped green onion.</p>
</li>
<li><p>Delicately mix your thinly sliced meat and meatballs in the marinade, and set aside to do it’s thing.</p>
</li>
<li><p>At this point you can finish your broth.  Bring your kombu pot to a boil and immediately remove the kombu once it starts to boil (WARNING, make sure to not boil the kombu, it’ll turn your broth all slimy and icky if you do).  Once you remove your kombu, discard it, and toss in your bonito flakes.  Turn your pot on low, cover, and let steep for about 15 minutes.  After you let it steep, strain the broth to remove the bonito flakes, return the resulting broth to your pot and allow some ginger and garlic to steep in the broth using a tea ball or small strainer set into the broth.  Or I mean hell you can throw the garlic and ginger in there and strain it again, that’s kind of a hassle though in my opinion. Add the <strong>heaping tablespoon of light miso </strong>to dissolve in the broth and a splash of soy sauce and mirin.</p>
</li>
<li><p>While your broth is working, arrange your veggies and some meat in your hot pot, reserving some meat and maybe some veggies on a plate to cook as the meal goes on.</p>
</li>
<li><p>Pour your strained broth over the veggies in your hot pot and spoon some of your (hopefully) fluffy rice into serving bowls.  I also poured a touch of my meat marinade in there, no worries, the heat will kill of any harmful bacteria.  Grab some chopsticks and a ladle, whatever pickled side dishes and sauces you want, as well as the rest of your reserved meat and veggies, and meet your friends and family around the pot.</p>
</li>
<li><p>Cover your hot pot with the lid and turn the heat on to simmer.  While your first course is bubbling away, chat with your friends or family, drink a beer or take a shot, flirt with your longtime crush.  <em>The point is, </em>have fun with your people, enjoy their company.  Laugh until your gut hurts, and your eyes water. After all, that’s the main component of any hot pot meal : <strong><em>enjoying a delicious meal with your friends and family.</em></strong></p>
</li>
<li><p>When the first batch is done, eat away, add more food to the pot as it’s eaten, and please - enjoy.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/hotPot3.jpg" alt="image alt text"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/hotPot4.jpg" alt="image alt text"></p>
<p><strong><strong>Also, I realize this may seem like quite a bit of work, but honestly it’s all prep work.  The actual cooking is done around your cooking vessel with your peeps.  And if you enjoy cooking just as much I do, you’ll enjoy shuffling barefoot around your kitchen with a beer in your hand listening to your favorite music for an hour while you prep for a truly, soon-to-be memorable meal with your friends and family.</strong></strong></p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miso Hot Pot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/hotPot1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Miso Hot Pot&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/Ho
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Veggie Lasagna</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/25/lasagna/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/25/lasagna/</id>
    <published>2017-01-26T02:19:28.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-26T02:39:29.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_202723.jpg" alt="Lasagna"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_200316.jpg" alt="Lasagna"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_191509.jpg" alt="Lasagna"></p>
<p><strong>This veggie lasagna, I gotta say, was probably the best I’ve ever made. It was tomatoey and full of herbs, garlic and onions, a cheesy ricotta mixture with just the right amount of salt, and a splash of balsamic vinegar. Layers of zucchini come together with the sauce and cheese to provide just the right amount of bite. Oh! And the edges of the pasta were crispy. Geez, writing about it is making me hungry. The only thing I regret is that I should’ve added more veggies. Maybe like a ratatouille lasagna or something. . . . with spinach, spinach is good too. What can I say, I’m kind of a veg head. Alrighty then, here we go.</strong></p>
<p>Ingredients :</p>
<ul>
<li>Cooked lasagna noodles (fresh if possible, but that’s a tall order)</li>
<li>Small thing of ricotta</li>
<li>A bit of milk</li>
<li>Shredded mozzarella</li>
<li>Shredded parmesan</li>
<li>1 can of unsalted diced tomatoes</li>
<li>1 can of tomato puree or sauce</li>
<li>Tomato paste</li>
<li>An assortment of dried or fresh herbs (fresh is generally better, but dried will do in a pinch)        I used: dried basil, parsley, oregano, and a bit of ground rosemary, oh and a little red pepper flake.</li>
<li>Finely diced yellow onion, or you can grind it; it’ll cook faster and incorporate into the sauce better.</li>
<li>Plenty of fresh ground garlic</li>
<li>A splash of balsamic vinegar</li>
<li>Plenty of fresh veggies, I only used zucchini because it was hanging around my fridge on the verge of going bad, but you can use any veggie that would go well with the fresh tomato sauce.  Try thinly sliced eggplant, squash, or tomato and spinach.</li>
</ul>
<p>The How-to :</p>
<ul>
<li>Firstly, preheat your oven to about 350 degrees, and you’re also going to want to salt your veggie slices to draw out excess moisture. Doing this helps the veggies cook faster and more evenly when layered with the tomato sauce. It also prevents the lasagna from becoming “watery” when it’s baked.  It also help if you make the slices pretty thin. Lay the bowl of salted veggies to the side to do their thing.</li>
<li>Then you’re going to want to get your sauce going, which is going to take at least thirty minutes to simmer before you can use it. Forty-five minutes is optimal, but thirty works. The long simmering time allows the flavors to meld. Anyways, saute your onions until translucent, some char is good too. Season the onions with salt, pepper, your herbs, then add a good squirt of tomato paste. After you add the tomato paste, turn up the heat some and deglaze the pot with a generous splash of balsamic vinegar. Then you can add your cans of tomatos. Put the lid on caddy corner so that moisture can escape, turn the heat down to a simmer, and let it go.</li>
<li>Next you can start your noodles. Follow the directions on the box and make sure you salt and oil you noodle water.</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_202723.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lasagna&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_200
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Kimchi</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/24/Kimchi/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/24/Kimchi/</id>
    <published>2017-01-24T18:47:43.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-25T01:16:17.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="../../../../photos/first.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170123_165248.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><strong>Word-to-the Wise : Making kimchi is not for the faint of heart or culinarily unappreciative or lazy. You’re gonna be at this s$$t for a few hours, but trust me, it’s totally worth it.  Also, the key to anaerobic fermentation is sanitation, make sure everything is sterilized and clean before you start, right down to your itty bitty fingernails.</strong></p>
<h3 id="Ingredients"><a href="#Ingredients" class="headerlink" title="Ingredients:"></a>Ingredients:</h3><ul>
<li>Napa Cabbage (however many you plan on eating/storing, cut it, or them, into quarters with the butt, yes butt, for the immature, still intact but not sticking out. Giggle a little you know you want to)</li>
<li>Daikon radish (peeled and cut into thin matchsticks)</li>
<li>One carrot (also peeled and cut into matchsticks)</li>
<li>Green onion (roughly chopped)</li>
<li>Yellow onion (thinly sliced, not diced)</li>
<li>Enough salt to roughly cover each quarter and each individual leaf and enough to make a slightly salty small water bath.</li>
<li>A bit of sugar to help those good bacteria along</li>
<li>A few cloves of garlic and peeled ginger crushed together</li>
<li>Korean chilli flakes, preferably powder, enough to cover all of your cabbage leaves</li>
<li>Enough fish sauce to make a paste with the chilli flakes/powder (try to get the clearest sauce you can find)</li>
<li>A splash of rice vinegar over the finished product (if you want)</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="What-you’ll-need-to-make-it"><a href="#What-you’ll-need-to-make-it" class="headerlink" title="What you’ll need to make it :"></a>What you’ll need to make it :</h3><ul>
<li>A food grade container (plastic, a traditional clay crock, a glass jar, whatever)</li>
<li>Something to push all the cabbage down and hold it down (a rock or plate)</li>
<li>Something to rest the cabbage in the salt water bath and to rub the cabbage (I used my kitchen sink after I sterilized it with hot water and vinegar.  Remember, no bad bacteria)</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="The-How-to"><a href="#The-How-to" class="headerlink" title="The How-to :"></a>The How-to :</h3><ul>
<li>Firstly, cut the cabbage into long quarters</li>
<li>Fill your sink with salt water “salty like the sea, but not the dead sea”, just enough liquid so that it comes about halfway up the cabbages.</li>
<li>Rub sea salt into and between each cabbage leaf</li>
<li>Let the cabbages rest in the salt water bath for about 2 hours, or however long it takes them to go limp.  Remember to gently rotate the cabbages every so often.</li>
<li>While the cabbages are resting prep your daikon, carrot, green onion, yellow onion.  Go ahead and crush your garlic and ginger together as well, I used my mortar and pestle, but you can use a good food processor.</li>
<li>Mix together your chilli paste and fish sauce.  I used two cabbages, I ended up using a little less than a ½ cup of each.</li>
<li>Mix the ground ginger and garlic, your fish chilli paste, all of the cut veggies, and about a tablespoon of sugar.  Voila! Your kimchi paste.</li>
<li>So, your cabbages are nice and wilted from the salt, now the fun part.  Place your chosen fermentation vessel next to the sink so you can immediately transfer the cabbages.  After that rub the chilli vegetable mixture all over the cabbages as well as between the leaves, much like the same way you   rubbed the salt into the cabbage.  So do this until every quarter is nicely covered.</li>
<li>Arrange each cabbage in your fermentation vessel and press, pretty hard, into the cabbage.  Keep rubbing and arranging the cabbage, preferably so that they almost interlock, and press to release any trapped air.</li>
<li>Once you’re done, take a small plate or anything heavy and small enough to fit into the fermentation vessel.  Press hard onto the plate or whatever you used, hard enough to kinda squish the cabbages tighter and closer together.  The goal of this last step is to release any trapped air so that     your possibility of getting the wrong kind of bacteria lowers and your possibility of good, anaerobic bacteria increases.</li>
<li>After that, put your weight on the cabbages, and cover loosely with a large plate or lid.  Set it on your counter for about a week or however long it takes for the cabbages to fully ferment.  Afterwards store it in your fridge, it’ll keep a pretty long time so enjoy!</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170123_165445.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170124_120911.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170124_121015.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p></p><p style="font-size: 3em;
          text-align: center;">&diams;</p><p></p>
<h4 id="One-day-after"><a href="#One-day-after" class="headerlink" title="One day after"></a>One day after</h4><p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170124_121104.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170124_121109.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><em>Warning: Your house will probably start to smell pretty funky after a few days, but this is a good sign!  It means your cabbages have caught the good bacteria and are fermenting happily away. Bubbles that weren’t there in the beginning are also a good sign.  If any mold appears (which it 99.9% won’t with all the salt and chilli pepper in there) throw the batch out and start over.</em></p>
<p>Also, if you would like a more specific recipe <a href="http://www.maangchi.com/recipe/tongbaechu-kimchi" target="_blank" rel="external">check this link out</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/first.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kimchi&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../Photos/IMG_20170123_165248.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kimchi&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello everyone!</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/18/hello-world/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/18/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2017-01-19T02:09:16.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-19T04:12:18.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="My-Food-Porn"><a href="#My-Food-Porn" class="headerlink" title="My Food Porn"></a>My Food Porn</h2><p>Hi everybody, or whoever is reading, thanks for checking out my blog - My Food Porn! If you like home cooked, comfort food from all over the world, I think you will love my food! I like to experiment with any kind of food,<br>including many types of Asian (Vietnamese, Japanese, Chinese, etc.) as well as Italian (I’m part Italian, so it kind of makes sense I guess lol) as well as Southern food (I’m from Georgia), so no matter what kind of food you<br>like you will probably see something here you like (at least I hope so) with simple, easy to follow instructions on how you can make these meals yourself! Keep note though; my recipes are bare bones.<br>They aren’t exact by any means because my personal philosophy is that crafting food is not only an art but an expression of a culture.<br>I want people who see these pictures to take stock of what’s said and seen and take it and run wild with it.<br>Take it and make it your own, because food is every human being’s right.</p>
<p>I hope to post pretty regularly, at least twice a week, if possible. I absolutely cannot wait to share my food with you and I sincerely hope<br>you enjoy reading about it as much as I enjoy cooking it!</p>
<p>Also, if you would like to see some pictures (this is My Food Porn right (:) feel free to check out my gallery <a href="https://plus.google.com/collection/gLv5lB" target="_blank" rel="external">here</a>.</p>
<p>Thanks again!</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;My-Food-Porn&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#My-Food-Porn&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;My Food Porn&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;My Food Porn&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everybody, or whoever is re
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
