<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>My Food Porn</title>
  
  <link href="/MyFoodPorn/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/"/>
  <updated>2017-01-19T03:33:34.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Logan Griffis</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello everyone!</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/18/hello-world/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/18/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2017-01-19T02:09:16.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-19T03:33:34.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="My-Food-Porn"><a href="#My-Food-Porn" class="headerlink" title="My Food Porn"></a>My Food Porn</h2><p>Hi everybody, or whoever is reading, thanks for checking out my blog - My Food Porn* ! If you like home cooked, comfort food<br>from all over the world, I think you will love my food! I like to experiment with any kind of food, including<br>many types of Asian (Vietnamese, Japanese, Chinese, etc.) as well as Italian (I’m part Italian, so it kind of makes sense I guess lol)<br>as well as Southern food (I’m from Georgia), so no<br>matter what kind of food you like you will probably see something here you like (at least I hope so) with simple, easy to follow<br>instructions on how you can make these meals yourself! Keep note though; my recipes are bare bones.<br>They aren’t exact by any means because my personal philosophy is that crafting food is not only an art but an expression of a culture.<br>I want people who see these pictures to take stock of what’s said and seen and take it and run wild with it.<br>Take it and make it your own, because food is every human being’s right.</p>
<p>I plan on posting pretty regularly, atleast twice a week if possible. I cant wait to sahre my food with you and<br>I hope you enjoy reading about it as much as I like cooking it!</p>
<p>Also, if you would like to see some pictures (this is My Food Porn right (:) feel free to check out my gallery<br><a href="https://plus.google.com/collection/gLv5lB" target="_blank" rel="external">here</a>.</p>
<p>Thanks again!</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;My-Food-Porn&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#My-Food-Porn&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;My Food Porn&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;My Food Porn&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everybody, or whoever is re
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
