<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>My Food Porn</title>
  
  <link href="/MyFoodPorn/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/"/>
  <updated>2017-01-26T02:39:29.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Logan Griffis</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Veggie Lasagna</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/25/lasagna/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/25/lasagna/</id>
    <published>2017-01-26T02:19:28.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-26T02:39:29.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_202723.jpg" alt="Lasagna"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_200316.jpg" alt="Lasagna"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_191509.jpg" alt="Lasagna"></p>
<p><strong>This veggie lasagna, I gotta say, was probably the best I’ve ever made. It was tomatoey and full of herbs, garlic and onions, a cheesy ricotta mixture with just the right amount of salt, and a splash of balsamic vinegar. Layers of zucchini come together with the sauce and cheese to provide just the right amount of bite. Oh! And the edges of the pasta were crispy. Geez, writing about it is making me hungry. The only thing I regret is that I should’ve added more veggies. Maybe like a ratatouille lasagna or something. . . . with spinach, spinach is good too. What can I say, I’m kind of a veg head. Alrighty then, here we go.</strong></p>
<p>Ingredients :</p>
<ul>
<li>Cooked lasagna noodles (fresh if possible, but that’s a tall order)</li>
<li>Small thing of ricotta</li>
<li>A bit of milk</li>
<li>Shredded mozzarella</li>
<li>Shredded parmesan</li>
<li>1 can of unsalted diced tomatoes</li>
<li>1 can of tomato puree or sauce</li>
<li>Tomato paste</li>
<li>An assortment of dried or fresh herbs (fresh is generally better, but dried will do in a pinch)        I used: dried basil, parsley, oregano, and a bit of ground rosemary, oh and a little red pepper flake.</li>
<li>Finely diced yellow onion, or you can grind it; it’ll cook faster and incorporate into the sauce better.</li>
<li>Plenty of fresh ground garlic</li>
<li>A splash of balsamic vinegar</li>
<li>Plenty of fresh veggies, I only used zucchini because it was hanging around my fridge on the verge of going bad, but you can use any veggie that would go well with the fresh tomato sauce.  Try thinly sliced eggplant, squash, or tomato and spinach.</li>
</ul>
<p>The How-to :</p>
<ul>
<li>Firstly, preheat your oven to about 350 degrees, and you’re also going to want to salt your veggie slices to draw out excess moisture. Doing this helps the veggies cook faster and more evenly when layered with the tomato sauce. It also prevents the lasagna from becoming “watery” when it’s baked.  It also help if you make the slices pretty thin. Lay the bowl of salted veggies to the side to do their thing.</li>
<li>Then you’re going to want to get your sauce going, which is going to take at least thirty minutes to simmer before you can use it. Forty-five minutes is optimal, but thirty works. The long simmering time allows the flavors to meld. Anyways, saute your onions until translucent, some char is good too. Season the onions with salt, pepper, your herbs, then add a good squirt of tomato paste. After you add the tomato paste, turn up the heat some and deglaze the pot with a generous splash of balsamic vinegar. Then you can add your cans of tomatos. Put the lid on caddy corner so that moisture can escape, turn the heat down to a simmer, and let it go.</li>
<li>Next you can start your noodles. Follow the directions on the box and make sure you salt and oil you noodle water.</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_202723.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lasagna&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/lasagna/IMG_20170116_200
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Kimchi</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/24/Kimchi/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/24/Kimchi/</id>
    <published>2017-01-24T18:47:43.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-25T01:16:17.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="../../../../photos/first.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170123_165248.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><strong>Word-to-the Wise : Making kimchi is not for the faint of heart or culinarily unappreciative or lazy. You’re gonna be at this s$$t for a few hours, but trust me, it’s totally worth it.  Also, the key to anaerobic fermentation is sanitation, make sure everything is sterilized and clean before you start, right down to your itty bitty fingernails.</strong></p>
<h3 id="Ingredients"><a href="#Ingredients" class="headerlink" title="Ingredients:"></a>Ingredients:</h3><ul>
<li>Napa Cabbage (however many you plan on eating/storing, cut it, or them, into quarters with the butt, yes butt, for the immature, still intact but not sticking out. Giggle a little you know you want to)</li>
<li>Daikon radish (peeled and cut into thin matchsticks)</li>
<li>One carrot (also peeled and cut into matchsticks)</li>
<li>Green onion (roughly chopped)</li>
<li>Yellow onion (thinly sliced, not diced)</li>
<li>Enough salt to roughly cover each quarter and each individual leaf and enough to make a slightly salty small water bath.</li>
<li>A bit of sugar to help those good bacteria along</li>
<li>A few cloves of garlic and peeled ginger crushed together</li>
<li>Korean chilli flakes, preferably powder, enough to cover all of your cabbage leaves</li>
<li>Enough fish sauce to make a paste with the chilli flakes/powder (try to get the clearest sauce you can find)</li>
<li>A splash of rice vinegar over the finished product (if you want)</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="What-you’ll-need-to-make-it"><a href="#What-you’ll-need-to-make-it" class="headerlink" title="What you’ll need to make it :"></a>What you’ll need to make it :</h3><ul>
<li>A food grade container (plastic, a traditional clay crock, a glass jar, whatever)</li>
<li>Something to push all the cabbage down and hold it down (a rock or plate)</li>
<li>Something to rest the cabbage in the salt water bath and to rub the cabbage (I used my kitchen sink after I sterilized it with hot water and vinegar.  Remember, no bad bacteria)</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="The-How-to"><a href="#The-How-to" class="headerlink" title="The How-to :"></a>The How-to :</h3><ul>
<li>Firstly, cut the cabbage into long quarters</li>
<li>Fill your sink with salt water “salty like the sea, but not the dead sea”, just enough liquid so that it comes about halfway up the cabbages.</li>
<li>Rub sea salt into and between each cabbage leaf</li>
<li>Let the cabbages rest in the salt water bath for about 2 hours, or however long it takes them to go limp.  Remember to gently rotate the cabbages every so often.</li>
<li>While the cabbages are resting prep your daikon, carrot, green onion, yellow onion.  Go ahead and crush your garlic and ginger together as well, I used my mortar and pestle, but you can use a good food processor.</li>
<li>Mix together your chilli paste and fish sauce.  I used two cabbages, I ended up using a little less than a ½ cup of each.</li>
<li>Mix the ground ginger and garlic, your fish chilli paste, all of the cut veggies, and about a tablespoon of sugar.  Voila! Your kimchi paste.</li>
<li>So, your cabbages are nice and wilted from the salt, now the fun part.  Place your chosen fermentation vessel next to the sink so you can immediately transfer the cabbages.  After that rub the chilli vegetable mixture all over the cabbages as well as between the leaves, much like the same way you   rubbed the salt into the cabbage.  So do this until every quarter is nicely covered.</li>
<li>Arrange each cabbage in your fermentation vessel and press, pretty hard, into the cabbage.  Keep rubbing and arranging the cabbage, preferably so that they almost interlock, and press to release any trapped air.</li>
<li>Once you’re done, take a small plate or anything heavy and small enough to fit into the fermentation vessel.  Press hard onto the plate or whatever you used, hard enough to kinda squish the cabbages tighter and closer together.  The goal of this last step is to release any trapped air so that     your possibility of getting the wrong kind of bacteria lowers and your possibility of good, anaerobic bacteria increases.</li>
<li>After that, put your weight on the cabbages, and cover loosely with a large plate or lid.  Set it on your counter for about a week or however long it takes for the cabbages to fully ferment.  Afterwards store it in your fridge, it’ll keep a pretty long time so enjoy!</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170123_165445.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170124_120911.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170124_121015.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p></p><p style="font-size: 3em;
          text-align: center;">&diams;</p><p></p>
<h4 id="One-day-after"><a href="#One-day-after" class="headerlink" title="One day after"></a>One day after</h4><p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170124_121104.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><img src="../../../../Photos/IMG_20170124_121109.jpg" alt="Kimchi"></p>
<p><em>Warning: Your house will probably start to smell pretty funky after a few days, but this is a good sign!  It means your cabbages have caught the good bacteria and are fermenting happily away. Bubbles that weren’t there in the beginning are also a good sign.  If any mold appears (which it 99.9% won’t with all the salt and chilli pepper in there) throw the batch out and start over.</em></p>
<p>Also, if you would like a more specific recipe <a href="http://www.maangchi.com/recipe/tongbaechu-kimchi" target="_blank" rel="external">check this link out</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../photos/first.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kimchi&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../Photos/IMG_20170123_165248.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kimchi&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello everyone!</title>
    <link href="https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/18/hello-world/"/>
    <id>https://jgw96.github.io/MyFoodPorn/2017/01/18/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2017-01-19T02:09:16.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-19T04:12:18.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="My-Food-Porn"><a href="#My-Food-Porn" class="headerlink" title="My Food Porn"></a>My Food Porn</h2><p>Hi everybody, or whoever is reading, thanks for checking out my blog - My Food Porn! If you like home cooked, comfort food from all over the world, I think you will love my food! I like to experiment with any kind of food,<br>including many types of Asian (Vietnamese, Japanese, Chinese, etc.) as well as Italian (I’m part Italian, so it kind of makes sense I guess lol) as well as Southern food (I’m from Georgia), so no matter what kind of food you<br>like you will probably see something here you like (at least I hope so) with simple, easy to follow instructions on how you can make these meals yourself! Keep note though; my recipes are bare bones.<br>They aren’t exact by any means because my personal philosophy is that crafting food is not only an art but an expression of a culture.<br>I want people who see these pictures to take stock of what’s said and seen and take it and run wild with it.<br>Take it and make it your own, because food is every human being’s right.</p>
<p>I hope to post pretty regularly, at least twice a week, if possible. I absolutely cannot wait to share my food with you and I sincerely hope<br>you enjoy reading about it as much as I enjoy cooking it!</p>
<p>Also, if you would like to see some pictures (this is My Food Porn right (:) feel free to check out my gallery <a href="https://plus.google.com/collection/gLv5lB" target="_blank" rel="external">here</a>.</p>
<p>Thanks again!</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;My-Food-Porn&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#My-Food-Porn&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;My Food Porn&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;My Food Porn&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everybody, or whoever is re
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
